JAN PAULO S. GOZUM

+1(916)307-8111)| +63(917)653-4136 (Whatsapp, Viber, Telegram)| 13109 Dunrobin Ave, Downey, CA 90242-4914 paugozum1@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/jan-paulo-gozum-b563a5172/ https://github.com/paupaugoz

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Around 3 ½ years of front-end development experience with (SDLC life cycle) analysis, design, development, testing and deploying web applications through AWS and other cloud-based platforms. I have created web applications using Ruby-on-Rails, and have extensive experience with NodeJS, and ExpressJS as well as experience with React. Versatile, adaptive and a quick-learner working with varied clients in **real-estate**, **paper**, **telecommunications**, **sports**, **startups**, **and government**. I strive to deliver responsive, functional, and user-centered UI that are aligned with business objectives, and goals in an Agile environment. **SKILLS**

- Expertise in HandlebarsJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Bootstrap,
- Expertise in HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, Semantic HTML5, SASS, Ruby on Rails, Git, NPM, JQuery
- Intermediate knowledge of React.js, Angular.JS
- Web application implementation and development
- AGILE development, UX/UI Architecture, SEO
- Familiarity with Figma, Jest, C++, Python
- Familiarity with C#, Gulp, TypeScript

WORK EXPERIENCE

Hidalgo Land Development Corporation - Real-estate (Front End Developer, Aug 2018 to May 2019)

Worked as a solo front-end developer; creating a real-estate materials procurement web application built on ExpressJS using the Handlebars templating engine which saved client thousands of dollars upon deployment

- Transformed 57 figma mockups into .handlebars views (HTML/CSS with Handlebars templating)
- Created API calls and route requests
- Aided with integration of front, and backend, as well as deployment of web application to AWS
- Created separate views for user roles & authentication (Engineer, Management, Warehouse, Encoder)
- Involved with whole SDLC phase from start to finish

La Purisima - Paper Supplier (Front-end Developer, January 2018 - May 2018)

Worked on an online-ordering system using Ruby on Rails for a family-run paper company

- Created a full-stack web application for an admin page to monitor ordering, and processing of orders
- Utilized Webpack, and PostgreSQL

Smart Communications, Inc - Telecommunications (Front-end Junior Developer, May 2018 - August 2017)

Worked as an intern, under the customer relations IT department; tasked with wireframing, and templating of the proposed new customer rewards program

- Designed, and created wireframes, and mockups for the company's proposed customer rewards site
- Transformed design mockups into HTML/CSS prototypes using Twitter Bootstrap

Tiebreaker Times - Sports News (Front-end Intern, January 2017 - April 2017) (https://tiebreakertimes.com.ph/)

Maintained and updated website, and implemented new pages for addition of sports

- Utilized HTML/CSS to redesign parts of website for better layouting
- Employed Semantic HTML for better rankings

Marikina Public Market - Government (Website Developer, September 2016 - November 2016)

Redesigned Wordpress website for public market using HTML/CSS

EDUCATION

Ateneo de Manila University, Philippines

Expected Graduation Date: June 2019

Bachelor of Science: Management Information Systems

Specialization: Data Science and Analytics

Extracurricular

- Created 3 open-source scripts used by thousands for a cryptocurrency bot to visualize where the bot would buy and sell to backtest strategies (https://www.tradingview.com/u/paupaugozum/#published-scripts)
- UX Society, Management Information Systems Association
- Ateneo Hackathon 3rd place
- Ateneo de Manila University Varsity Judo Team